# j,lkjhgg k.jhbvgjucv Mudau

#### Personal details

Contact number: 0764714796

Email address: mudau7tony3@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 2006-11-29

Residential Area: 10 Richmond street, Crystal Park, Benoni, Gauteng

## About me

I am an honest and hard-working individual who believes in quality work, continuous learning and sharing information. I am interested in learning data science, big-data, mechine learning, user experience and digital marketing. My life goal is to contribute to education and financial innovation in Africa. I currently code using python

#### Education

2014 - 5252 National Senior Certificate

School: huoiu

2014 - 5252 National Senior Certificate

School: huoiu

### Online Certificates

2013-2016 National Senior Certificate

School: St Francis College

2017-2021 Bachelor of Economics Honours

**Rhodes University** 

#### Skills

Computer Skills -

- python

- SQL

Interperonal Skills - Good communicator

	- Planner - Alert
Computer Skills	
	- - python
	- - SQL
Work Experience	
2019-2018	- Tutor - - - python
	- - SQL
2019-2018	- Tutor - - - python - - SQL
Volunteering	
2019-2018	- Student Volunteer
References	
Contact:	hgkgfkjtykj gjhgfjfgjhj ghjhfjfjrf